https://www.simmsfishing.com/discover/service/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Simms Fishing Products respects your privacy and recognizes your need for appropriate protection and management of your personal information such as your name, address, credit card, and e-mail. We recognize that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner. Simms Fishing Products has created this policy to inform you how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our web site.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT
We intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit Simms Fishing Products on the web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Consistent with most sites, we do log your internet address to give us an idea of which parts of our web site you visit and how long you spend there, but we do not link your internet address of your computer to anything personally identifiable.
There are times when we request that you voluntarily provide information such as your name, address, credit card, and e-mail. Generally this information is requested when you register for an on-line service or when you provide information in connection with an on-line transaction. Simms Fishing Products may occasionally use this information for internal marketing purposes, including our e-mail newsletter and catalog mailing. Simms Fishing Products will never sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.
SECURITY OF DATA
This site has reasonable security measures in place to protect the unauthorized access loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.
On-line transactions are safe with our secure shopping cart. This cart eliminates the possibility, however small, that someone might capture and view your personal information (such as a credit card number) while it is en route over the internet.
LINKS
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Simms Fishing Products is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.
POLICY SUBJECT TO CHANGE
If we decide to change our privacy practices, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always kept informed of what data we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Please check this page for changes from time to time to make sure you are aware of our latest privacy practices.
We are committed to continuing to protect the privacy of our customers.
